# Narendra Jasti

Dublin, Ireland.

Mobile: +353(0) 894602682 Email: narendrajasti50@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/narendra-

jasti-514275152/

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Completed Masters in Cloud Computing from National College of Ireland (NCI), having 6 months of experience as an Intern Web Developer with hands-on experience across various network frameworks like Angular js and React. My emphasis is on the position of Front-End Developer. Actively seeking fulltime opportunities for graduate roles. Eligible to work without restrictions for 2 years. Under Stamp 1 G graduate visa schema.

### **SKILLS**

## Web Developer skills

- Developed responsive and user-friendly website and pages.
- Creation and development of good Landing pages and Web application
- Used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and jQuery environment for development.
- Used CSS for designing and ensure cross-browser compatibility.
- Deploy website from local environment to live servers
- Integrated social media web services on website.

#### **Familiar IDE Skills:**

Microsoft Visual Studio, ATOM

### **Programming Languages:**

• Python, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Core Java, SQL

### **Other Skills:**

• Familiar with Ubuntu, Git, Microsoft Office 365, Data Structures, VM Ware, Devops.

## **Certifications:**

• Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Certified

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Freelancer Web Developer for CHASKA website | Dublin, Ireland | January 2020 – March 2020

### Roles and Responsibility:

- Developed dynamic and interactive website that ensured pageviews and user experience.
- Designed and developed user-friendly website, including optimized food order page that increased user clicks.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functions and speed.
- Designed processes for performance environment

# Web Developer (Guntur Government Hospital) | June 2018 - November 2018

• The project overcame the lacunae of hefty paperwork and slow management by creating a simple user-friendly web interface generating concurrent id and corresponding bar code format. This increased the registration speed.

### **EDUCATION**

## Master of Science – Computing in Cloud Computing | 2019-2020

National College of Ireland | Dublin | Ireland

Thesis Project: Supervisor: https://www.linkedin.com/in/horaciogy/

### Enhancing the performances of virtual machines in cloud computing by using Novel Round Robin.

- Enhancing the execution time of the performance of tasks from users to virtual machine.
- •Changing the traditional round robin algorithm into dynamic round robin algorithm by using mathematical methods of mean and median.
- Using real time workloads datasets for checking the performance of round robin and dynamic round robin for the virtual machines in cloud environment.

**Modules:** Cloud Architecture, Cloud Security, Cloud Infrastructure Management, Utility computing, Business Strategies of cloud computing, Virtualization, Data storage and management and Research in Computing.

# Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Science Engineering | 2014-2018

Vignan University | Guntur | India

## Final Year Project (Bachelor of Engineering) | Dec 2017 - April 2018

• In this, we proposed a notion called revocable-storage identity-based encryption (RS-IBE), which can provide the forward/backward security of ciphertext by introducing the functionalities of user revocation and ciphertext update simultaneously.

## **Deloitte Virtual Internship (Practical modules)**

Client Discovery, Design a Business Case, Considerations for Mobilisation, Define the project approach, Conduct a market scan, Further analysis & solution presentation, Understanding Cloud Computing, Cloud Feasibility Assessment and Cloud Readiness Assessment

### **HOBBIES:**

- Cricket
- Chess
- Technology Enthusiast

#### **LANGUAGES**

• Proficiency in English

### Leadership:

- Fulfilled the responsibility as a Class Representative for CSE-B during 3rd and 4th year.
- Served as the coordinator for the CSE department during college fest "SRUJANANKURA 2017".
- Initiated College event "V CODE 2017" as the technical assistant at Vignan University.
- Leading a cricket team on a competition conducted by vignan university and were runners-up out of 12 teams.